Things were busy that summer.
The frequent disasters of the
past year probably played a role,
but cursed spirits were
springing up like maggots.
Exercise, absorb, over and over.
Exercise, absorb.
No one else understands.
What cursed spirits taste like.
They taste like swallowing down a dirty
rag used to clean up shit and vomit.
Exercise.
Absorb.
What I witnessed isn't uncommon.
I understood the ugliness of the masses.
And still, I chose to be a
Jujutsu sorcerer who saves others.
That's what I've been telling
myself ever since that day.
ever since that day.
Apparently,
this used to be the home of
the president of a company
who managed a local chain
of barbecue restaurants.
However, in July of last year, remember
that whole mad cow disease problem?
Well, it dealt a fatal blow to his
restaurants and buried him in debt.
He wound up committing
suicide with his family.
Ever since then, local rumors claim
the president's home was haunted.
High school students, college students,
lots of people started visiting
the place as a test of courage.
Then they started going missing.
Those rumors only brought about
more rumors, and the damage
just continued to spread.
Haunted locations have always attracted
a high quotient of speculation.
And nowadays, thanks to the internet,
rumors can spread at an
Unbelievable speed that means
it's all just even more work
for us Jujutsu sorcerers to
investigate and eliminate in
addition to the older victims
there were three young kids who
went missing on their way home
from school there's also a high
probability that the families
police staff co-workers and
friends who trace the paths
of those who disappear will
find that they become victims
themselves we have to sever the
root of this problem quickly
hq sent us to investigate because
they reached the same conclusion
they're even paying my fees
which aren't cheap Mei Mei,
did you overcharge them again?
You make it sound so bad?
Call it negotiation!
We're here.
Okay, let's go then.
Emerge from darkness, black or still.
Purified that there's
no need for a veil huh?
I don't sense the presence
of any curses around here.
The cause is almost certainly
inside of the building.
You can cast the veil later.
If we end up attacking it
from outside, it's open.
Seems like something's
blocking the door, though.
What is this?
Mei Mei.
It's here.
And it's all around us, too.
Let's get going.
I don't need that, but you do. Right.
Thanks, I really do.
Much better.
Incredible.
Oh, it still has electricity.
For now, let's just have a look around.
I'll take this floor.
You take the second.
Huh?
All by myself?
Is there a problem with that?
No, it's fine.
Good.
I'm counting on you.
Okay.
This is the last one.
Huh?
You've got some impressive pumps there.
Jeez, please don't startle me like that.
You were already startled
before I got here.
Are you done exploring the first floor?
Hmm?
This is the first floor.
Huh?
I was walking down the first
floor's hallway when I found you.
What? No way.
I know I entered a room
at the end of the hallway.
Huh.
A box of candy.
A bag of potato chips a can a backpack a
sweatshirt i've already seen these things?
Three times see these
marks along the wall i
left them to mark my way
so i wouldn't get lost.
Well well it would seem that we're
already in the belly of the beast!
Huh?
For real?
How long can this hallway possibly be?
It just goes on.
We've been walking for 30 minutes.
That's about four kilometers so far.
It's not an innate domain, is it?
It's not.
This is a manifestation of the
spirit's mindscape, which means...
This is a barrier.
Correct.
Most likely the victims
were trapped inside this,
and then killed by the cursed spirit.
Though considering the
use of this technique,
the cursed spirit itself should be weak.
All we need to do is escape this barrier.
Now, quiz time.
Tell me, Utahime, how would
you break this barrier?
This hallway is repeating itself.
At first, I...
At first, I thought...
I'm surprised you could touch that.
At first, I thought it
was shaped like a donut.
But we passed four of the
marks you made right I
calculated how many paces
were between them and got
122 203 157
and 270 so the
spacing between your marks
were completely random go
on the interval between
individual repetitions
isn't standardized which
means that there's a very
good possibility this
barrier is patching spaces
together so if we both
run down the hallway at top
speed then at some point
it'll break hmm very close 90 points
where did i lose 10 points when we run
we run in opposite directions
in sync now I see so my patching
theory was accurate then And if we
quickly run in opposite directions,
that makes it harder for the cursed
spirit to hold the barrier together.
And once we have that opening,
we might be able to get out.
One hundred points.
Well, that's settled.
If this works, then, I'm
counting on you for my promotion.
How much do you have in savings? What?
Never mind.
I'll think about it.
Fine. Okay.
Ready?
Go!
We did it!
I'm here to save you!
Utahime?
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
You crying? No! I'm not crying!
Be more polite!
If I was crying, would you console me?
I'd definitely like that.
But you wouldn't cry, Mae.
You're strong.
Not so.
Gojo!
Don't listen to me!
I don't need your help!
Don't swallow it.
I'll absorb it later.
Satoru, it's not nice to
pick on the weak, you know?
Okay, but what kind of idiot?
Picks on the strong.
You're the one naturally
fanning the flames, Code.
Uchihime!
Are you okay?
Shouko!
I was so worried about you.
We hadn't heard from
you for two whole days.
Shouko!
No!
Shoko, don't let yourself
turn out like those two!
I'm not trash like they
are, and I never will be.
Don't let yourself turn out like Utahime.
Ah, shut up.
Huh?
Wait, two days?
Ah, was the cursed spirits barrier
one of those that messes with time?
They're rare, but they
do happen now and then.
It is odd it took so long
since Mei was with you.
That would make sense.
Hm? Something wrong?
Not really, but actually that means
it involved two full days of labor.
So I was just thinking
about how to rewrite
the invoice for extra fees now owed to me.
She's planning to overcharge again.
More importantly, what about...
the veil? Huh?
Hm? Hm?
Next up, yesterday's large explosion
rocked Shizoka prefecture...
You three were supposed to
oversee the mission at that home.
Also,
you left your assistant
supervisor behind and on
top of everything you forgot
the veil who's to blame
Sensei, I'm asking you to stop
this hunt for the culprits.
So it was you then
Is a veil even really
necessary in the first place
Not like it matters if
normie see it or not right.
They can't see curse spirits
or curse techniques anyway
but it's not good if they do see them the
strongest deterrent against the outbreak
of a cursed spirit is the mental calm
of the populace that's exactly why we
have to conceal all of these threats as
much as possible to make sure they never
ever get to see them
and that's not looking
out
for
the weak and
protecting them is
honestly so exhausting survival of the
weakest that's the proper shape of a proper
society the weak help each other and
discourage strength listen
Satoru jujutsu exists
to protect non jujutsu sorcerers moral
arguments I hate moral arguments what
assigning reasons and responsibility to
strength is what those
who are weak tend to do.
When are you going to quit making yourself
feel better by spouting all this bullshit?
Perfect time for a smoke break.
Want to take this outside,
Satoru?
Why, you feeling lonely?
Go by yourself if you want.
Hmm.
How long are you going
to keep fooling around?
Where did Shoko go? Who knows?
Little girl's room?
Whatever.
This mission is being
assigned to you two anyway.
What are those faces for?
Oh, nothing.
Frankly, I think it's too much for you.
But Tengen asked for you specifically.
Your mission has two goals.
The star plasma vessel is the
one compatible with Tengen.
You are to escort that girl and erase her.
Escort some brat and then erase her.
That's right.
He's finally gone senile.
It is spring.
His head's probably full with
being the next principle.
All jokes aside though that
didn't sound like a joke to me.
Is this about renewing Tingen's
technique. Huh? What's that?
What'd I miss?
Tengen possesses the curse technique of
immortality, but it's not eternal youth.
Not a problem if all he did was get older,
but after his body ages
to a certain point,
the curse technique
begins rewriting his body.
Evolution.
He'll cease to be human and
become a higher form of existence.
What's so bad about that?
Sounds sweet.
According to Tengen,
those who reach that state of
being no longer have any free will.
It means that Tengen would
cease to be Tengen any longer.
All the Jujutsu schools,
the barriers that form the
foundation of Jujutsu society,
the many barrier techniques
of the assistant supervisors,
they're all being strengthened by Tengen.
And without the aid of his power,
we could hardly maintain security
or clean up after missions.
In the worst-case scenario, Tengen
could even become a threat to mankind.
That's why every 500 years he
finds the Plasma Star Vessel,
someone who is compatible with him,
and he assimilates them, overriding
the information of their body.
By Tengen renewing his form,
he resets his curse technique to
the start and avoids evolution.
I get it now.
It would be fine if he
digivolved into Metal Greymon,
but we can't have him
turning into Skull Greymon,
so we helped start him off
from the beginning at Coromon.
What?
Whatever works, I guess.
The location of the Star Plasma
Vessel has unfortunately been leaked.
Right now,
there are two major groups who are
simultaneously after the young girl's life.
One is the Curse User Group, Q.
They seek to upend Jujutsu
society with Tengen's rampage.
The other is the Star Religious Group,
also known as the Time Vessel Association,
who worships Tengen as a god.
But Tengen will assimilate the Star
Plasma Vessel in just two days' time.
You are to protect this
young girl till then,
and ensure that Tengen reaches
her before the others do.
If you fail, the effects will ripple
throughout even normal society.
So put your heart into this!
You know,
I get why Curse User Group
Q would be after her,
but why would the Star Religious
Group want to kill some young kid?
Their object of worship is
the pure form of Tengen,
Allowing the Star Plasma Vessel,
an impurity in their minds,
to blend into him is unforgivable.
The Star Religious Group is
made up of non-sorcerers.
I don't think we need
to pay them any mind.
The ones to be wary of are definitely Q.
Oh, I'm sure it'll be fine.
We are the strongest, after all.
I mean, that's why Tengen asked
for us specifically, right?
Uh, huh? What is it?
You know, Satoru, I've been
meaning to say this for a while.
I think you should really stop
being so full of yourself.
Huh?
Especially when you're
addressing your superiors.
We might end up meeting Tengen soon.
You really should be
more polite and humble.
It would make you less threatening
to the juniors as well.
Yeah, screw that.
Come on, Satoru.
Whatever.
We can talk about it later.
Coming!
Huh?
You alive?
I'm still breathing.
You think we'll be blamed
if the kid died from that?
Uh-oh.
Don't blame me.
Hate Tengen if you must hate anyone
What?
Would you please stop
making us stand out so much?
We just got called out for that this morning
So this girl is the Star Plasma Vessel?
Those uniforms.
Your sorceress from Jujutsu High.
Hand over the kid.
Or I'll kill you!
Can't quite hear you.
Come closer so we can talk.
Nice catch.
That was a close one.
Wonderful.
You're Satoru Gojo, right?
You're famous.
I hear you're strong.
Let me find out if the rumors are true.
Sure, I'm game.
But let's set some rules.
Rules?
You see, I don't want to get
yelled at for going overboard.
So if you cry and apologize,
then I won't kill you.
That's our rule.
You damn punk!
It has started.
The Star Religious Group doesn't have the
power to fight against Jujutsu Sorcerers,
but they can pay very well.
That I guarantee.
How about it, Zenin?
Want to get in on the assassination
of the Star Plasma Vessel?
I'm not a Zenin anymore.
I took my wife's name.
It's Fushiguro now.
But sure, count me in on all the fun.
I don't want to hear anything
What place I'm doing is there?
I'm sure I'm not here.
I'm not here.
I'm not sure why I'm here.
I'm not sure what I'm saying.
I've seen a lot of things.
You know, the sky is dark,
I'm afraid of the sky.
I'm not looking at it.
You know how some words
get stuck in your head,
yeah, like homeowners
association requirements.
Uh-huh, or like universal healthcare.
Please watch the next
episode, Hidden Inventory 2.
What's yours, Shoko?
Fried chicken shop. Oh.